The Simpsons - Series 19
Episode 7 - Husbands & Knives
Subtitles by STS
Lame lame lame lame have it - lame
Superman dies Aquaman dies
Casper dies Caveman Robin
Black Robin Born-again Robin
Whoa - the infamous Wolverine
comic with pop-out claws
Why was this so controversial...
nice work DR Boo-hoo...
your tears have smudged
Wolverine's iconic sideburns
Hence you must by this comic...
and the cost of your innocent
accident is.....
twenty-five dollars please...
but that's the money
Yiayia Sophia...
gave me for Greek Orthodox Easter
I hate when they tell me
things about themselves
You should stop being so mean
to us kids
Well I suppose you could buy
your comics somewhere else...
maybe they sell comics at
the dry cleaners...
no, perhaps they sell comics
at the mattress store...
or perhaps you could
buy your comics at...
that new comic book store
across the street
Phillip K Dick it can't be...
it's as if Superman
moved to Gotham City...
which he did in
Worlds Finest Comics Number 94
See...
it was an imaginary story
dreamt by Jimmy Olsen...
after he was kicked in the head
by Supergirl's horse Comet...
it never really happened...
none of these things
ever really happen...
get out of my store
Grand Opening
Hey word up you guys...
how g-g-goes it...
my name's Milo and
this is Coolsville...
now listen, before everyone chills
with some sweet comic...
everyone gets a free piece of
japanese hard candy...
one for you short kid in back...
down low go long
I got prawn
I got miso
I got Dolphin
Now I hope you all like Korean
pop covers of Tom Jones songs...
cause they're about to be blasted
Sings 'What's up
Pussycat' in Korean
Asterix. Tin-Tin.
I heard these are only available
in high school french classes
Come on Snowy
We must save the
Belgian Ambassador...
from the Black Orchid Gang
What's that?
a shot of ignition?
zoot-a-loft.
this castle is actually
a four stage rocket...
and it's headed straight for
the Pompidou centre
Oh no I ripped it
Hey no worries little lady...
these books are meant to be
read and enjoyed...
not hoarded and then sold
when you get divorced.
various expressions of
wonderment form all...
all right I get it...
you're cool you're
not mainstream...
you wear a pork pie hat...
mmmmmm pork pie...
let's see what you know about
super heroes
Hey. I'm all about the capes
Flame on...
who's stronger the Thung
or the Mulk and show you're work...
woo hoo Head rush
OK. Well the Mulk kicked
a tidal wave into the sun
Whereas the Thung gave a piggy
back ride to the 1985 Chicago Bears
Hoo boy that's a tough one
What do you think?
you want to know what I think?
does Gallactus eat planets?
of course I do
Wow. I was in such a bad
relationship with my...
ex comic book guy
I forgot how good it could be
Mmmmmm
Bye Bart enjoy your funny books
Look Maggie I'm Wonder Woman
Wo-ah I've lost my perfect
26-26-26 figure
Never compare yourself to a stand E
Hey you're way skinnier
then a lot of super-heroes
Girthquake, Labarella
Kearney's mom
Shut Up her depression
medication...
makes her bloated
She's depressed
because you're so lame
Shut up.
Woo, I better join the Gym before
I go from hippy to hippo
I wish my mom said cute
things like that...
she can't because she's depressed
Shut up.
look at all these alternative
comic book creators
Alan Moore
Art Spiegleman
Dan Clowes
I've really identified with
the girls in Ghost World...
they made me feel like
I wasn't so alone...
yeah yeah whatever
Do you know anyone who
works at Batman...
because I really want to
draw Batman
I'm awesome at utility belts
check these out
This is where the Batman
keeps his money...
in case he has to take the bus
Uh huh
Alan Moore, you wrote my
favourite issues of
Radioactive Man
Oh really...
so you liked that I made your
favourite superhero...
a heroin addicted jazz critic...
who's not radioactive
I don't read the words. I just
like it when he punches people...
how do you make his costume
stick so close to his muscles
Mr Moore
Will you sign my DVD of
Watchman Babies...
which of the babies is
your favourite...
you see what those
bloody corporations do?
they take your ideas and
they suck them...
suck them like leeches
until they've gotten...
every last drop of the marrow
from your bones
Hey Tea-cup.
Why don't you chill out?
Very Well ...
Oh Little Lulu
I love yu-lu just the same haaaaa
Attention comic book aficionados
This man is not one of us
He has a girlfriend
My name's strawberry
my purse is a lunchbox
Now listen up...
my wayward little fan boys
I have the most wonderful news...
my store now sells ninja weapons
Whoa...
you would sell weapons of
the orient to children...
that is weak
Face it Fats Hasbeen
this man is the...
comic book guy our town deserves
Very well
I guess the mature
thing to do is...
Oh No the store's in trouble
League of Extraordinary
Freelancers
Activate
Mouse is in the House
How do you like this punchline?
oooh L.A.
This could be the gym for Me...
you're gunna get so ripped here...
we've got tummy tone with Sacha...
power bounce with Zac D.
Zen Abs with Zac G.
and you've just gotta try
mummy and me kickboxing...
who thought walking could
be so difficult...
well I'm sure everyone else
is having trouble too...
hmmmm maybe I'll just
hit the showers
Marge, you missed a spot
I wish there was a gym for
us regular ladies
Rules No Men.
No cell phones No mirrors
No Shame
Marge, I wish you well...
but why would women want
to go to a gym...
if there were no men there...
watching the and judging them
We're gunna be rich...
we can finally start a family
We have a family...
a better one
Switch stations
I love this gym...
me too
Finally an exercise bike
for women of a certain age
Jurassic aha ha ha ha
Mum every workout appointment
is booked up for months
We'll have to open a second Shapes
We just need to find a
vacant rental property
I can't believe the labour board
is shutting me down...
you lock your workers in at night
It's so they can't
tell their stories
Mr Krusty came to my village
He said he would marry me
No ring
just fill apple pies all day
Today's guest created
a womens only gym...
that's taken the tri-county
area by storm
Marge Simpson
Marge, I thank you
for creating Shapes...
and uh my boyfriend
thanks you too...
when is Straightman
going to pop the question?
uh uh.............
y'all getting german
cuckoo clocks...
you're getting a cuckoo clock...
and you're getting
a cuckoo clock...
and you're getting a cuckoo clock
Oh yeh Marge, I love
these business trips of yours...
the T.V. remote isn't nailed on...
my whole life I've never
been in a hotel that trusted me...
hors d'oeuvres, big
fancy desserts...
and my wife is paying
for everything...
now I know why pimps
are so happy...
yep nothing beats living on
'wife support'
I hear that...
yo guys,
come meet a new husband...
hey how yo doin?
I'm Homer...
my wife invented a gym for
'regular women'
my wife invested Sky Pills, she
mixed vitamins with alka-seltzer...
and pretended it was medicine
I pay ten dollars
a tube for those...
that's why I drive a Bentley
Yep. I haven't decided
what kind of new car to get...
you better decide soon as
I have a feeling...
your wife will also be getting
a new model...
yeh she'll be trading up...
and they're not
talking about cars...
are you sure they're
not talking about cars?
because those are car words
Homer, we're all second husbands...
as soon as our wives hit it big
they dumped the fat old guys...
they were with and married us
Marge won't dump me
I'm the anchor that
keeps her weighed down...
here's how it starts...
she gets a total make-over...
then she starts wearing
fancy new clothes...
then she stops wanting to
tell you about her day...
here's how you know she's
really about to go...
your wife seems happy
and full of life...
that will never happen
Marge. Marge.
the makeover...
oh my god the prophecy
is being fulfilled...
um so tell me about your day...
oh you don't want to hear about
my boring old day
I do. I do.
well the first inspirational
speech of the day...
was by the woman who climbed
Mt Everest...
and got everyone else killed.
hey the networks are different
channels in this city
It's O.K.
I don't care that you don't care...
go watch your thing...
are you happy and full of life
I sure am
Marge, now that you're rich...
you really should
get rid of that bag
Really' but I'm so
used to my old one
Old one? They're convincing
Marge to dump me
Oh it's easy
I get a new one every two years...
from Italy...
you would love a big black one
Marge, get away from them...
what's gotten into you?
I'm going to the successful
ladies room...
you guys have got to help me
If Marge leaves I'll have nothing
except my many friends...
and half the fortune
she is now making...
and will continue to make
Homer I'm going to let you in
on a secret
I'm a first husband
I used to look like this
What's your secret?
oh there's no secret
Just hard work uh-huh...
exercise two hours a day O.K.
keep up with the latest fashions
Fashions...
and of course cut out all
fatty foods and alcohol...
uh-huh uh-huh got it
I know just what it will take
to hang onto Marge
Mr Simpson let me outline...
the gastric bypass surgery
procedure for you O.K.
we put the band
around your stomach...
so that no solid food may enter...
you see just like so
It's a very very
serious operation...
you should only undergo it
as a last resort...
please doc. I know I'm not the...
greatest looking
guy in the world...
but I took care of my family
and that used to be enough...
but not anymore...
very well. If you wish...
we can perform the procedure
in the office today.
and I know how I can
knock myself out
I'll look at your bill
Hmm I guess considering all the
training you've received...
this is quite reasonable
I've never seen anything
so reasonable
It's the bargain of a lifetime
Dad are you O.K.
I see food on your plate
instead of blurring motions
Kids your daddy underwent a
special procedure...
so he can be more attractive
to your mother...
you had your hotdog plumped
No. I had my stomach stapled...
oh all food tastes like barf now
Homey I'm back...
[Marge Gasps]
Welcome home Marge
You remembered I like romance...
a smart successful
woman like you...
deserves the very best...
you also remembered
I like flattery...
do you like guys who are...
attractive
Homey, you look good...
all for you baby...
let me get a good look at you...
uh uh woah woah
slow down sexy beast...
why don't you take some time to
savor the front...
what are you hiding from me?
is it chocolate
It used to be...
woah - those buns
are poppin fresh...
yeah, I'm going to turn
off the lights now...
and I'll just fold this
old sweaty blanket...
and put it in the closet...
ow ow ow ow ow ow
Doctor, I'm embarrassed to show
my body to my wife...
and it's all because of
your surgery...
you want me to
unstaple your stomach...
no I want you to give me
every other surgery you have...
so I can look good...
and can you call it
an aortic valve replacement...
so my insurance will cover it...
no problem
O.K. count backwards from ten...
fine I admit it I'm drunk...
and so to honour her success
I bestow upon Marge Simpson...
this $100 gift card
to sweat pants etcetera...
did someone order a superstud?
oh my implants feel itchy...
yes I was out of silicone rubber...
so I used rolled up socks...
[crowd: gasps in horror]...
he's a monster...
pitchforks everyone...
monster, monster monster...
monster monster...
cut his heart out...
listen Homer
I've got to be honest with you...
you better not make me cry...
cause I don't know where
my tear ducts are anymore
I appreciate you trying to become
more attractive for me...
but the truth is
I'm way too successful for you now
I'm getting me a trophy husband
I don't want to live
without you Marge
O.K.
Huh? huh? what? hey.
why do I look like me again?
the doctor called me about all
the crazy surgeries you wanted...
and I said NO.
but I did have him
unstaple your stomach...
and turn you back into
the sweet man I love
It was all a dream?
I never became a hideous monster?
the only person who
thinks you're a monster...
is the one who had to give
you a sponge bath...
and dad I hope you
learned something from this
I sure have...
plastic surgery is a mistake...
because it hasn't been perfected
to where you look really good...
when it is everyone should get it
Amen...
listen Marge, I've been
wondering all these years...
what is it about me that
you find so irresistible?
lets face it you could do better...
well maybe I could...
but every time I look at you
I see the same adorable boy
I fell in love with...
ooohhh...
well there's nothing like
a happy ending
Holy Heavens.
is that a meteor heading
for the earth...
maybe but tonight
there's a benefit...
for underpaid comic book artists
of the 40's and 50's
to the cashbar
www.tvsubtitles.net