The Simpsons S19E06 (JABF22)
Little Orphan Millie
There is no such thing as an iPoddy.
Modern couch gag
10 couch gags to spice up your marriage
There's a bee on Maggie.
Okay, Maggie, just calmly and
carefully back away.
Beehive!
Blueberries!
I told you not to mock
me at picnics.
Uh, attention, everyone.
Uh, Luann and I
have some big news.
Is it that you're
brother and sister?
Because you really
look a lot alike.
No.
Half-brother
and half-sister?
No!
Siamese twins who've been
surgically separated?
No.
We're getting remarried.
- Oh, that's great.
- Great. Ooh, cool.
Way to go.
Many happy returns.
This is so awesome.
Finally you guys will stop using
me as a pawn in your fights.
Milhouse, you're
not a pawn.
I know, I know.
Did your father
say you were?
No. I swear.
I made it up.
Like kids do.
Well, now that we're
a family again,
you can stop your lying.
Homer.
The wedding's in 20 minutes.
Just pick a tie.
There are so many choices.
Bolo? Clip-on? Piano keys?
Ten Commandments of Beer?
The cornerstones
of the Brewish faith.
Why don't you wear a tie
that goes with my eyes?
And what color would that be?
You don't know what
color my eyes are?!
Of course I know.
No peeking.
I'm waiting.
Uh...
You really don't
know, do you?
Is "beautiful" a color?
No.
Marge, give me a break.
I don't notice the color
of people's eyes.
I just judge them on
the color of their skin.
Fine.
Since the color-- ah!--
of my eyes isn't-- ooh!--
important to you-- aah!--
then you don't get to-- Mmm!--
see them until you--
ow!-- remember.
Oh!
Please do not kick sea turtles
She's wearing white?
She must have rolled
the odometer back to zero.
So you're good at
noticing dress colors,
but not the eyes
that make your dinner.
We are gathered here in the sight of
God and this unsafe-for-swimming beach
to celebrate the holy un-divorcing
of Kirk and Luann.
Ow! What the...?
Little help?
Spaz.
Do you, Kirk,
take Luann to re-have and re-hold?
I do.
And do you, Luann, take Kirk--
despite the fact that he is
fundamentally the same man
that you said in court was unfit
to load your dishwasher?
Whose very touch repulsed you?
- Uh, your...
- Whose many annoying...
Uh, you're readingan
early draft of our vows.
Just say "I do."
I do.
You may now kiss the bride.
But make it quick.
The seagulls have gotten
into the hors d'oeuvres.
My friends, do not eat.
Is made with seagull meat.
See you in a week, Milhouse.
Have fun at the Simpsons'.
If you don't like
Mrs. Simpsons' cooking,
you have your "mommy meals."
I got 'em. Mm, mm.
Why does every kid who stays
with us bring "mommy meals"?
So I put pineapple
in my potato salad.
Live a little, huh?
That's why, to this day,
you never see a shark
with monkey arms.
Great story, Mr. Simpson.
But why do all your bedroom stories
have
commercials in them
for The Container Store?
Because if I do it enough,
maybe they'll start to pay me.
Sleep tight.
The Container Store, no wat
five convenient locations.
Ah... now that my mom and
dad are back together,
I'm happy every day.
I can't wait to wake up
so tomorrow can start.
Countdown to wake-up time
Whoa...
Uh-uh-uh.
We're gonna start
this marriage off right.
This time, I'm gonna carry you
over the threshold.
Dear God!
I need more nickels!
Luann, is that you
nibbling on my knee?
Check it out, an animal hole.
Where does it go?
Only one way to find out.
Ah...! Tarantulas!
I'll save you,
Baby Burps-A-Lot.
Ah...! Spider burps!
This week is the best.
I don't care if my parent
sever come back.
Milhouse Van Houten?
Yes?
Son, your parents
have been lost at sea.
I'm sorry.
Oh my God!
I said I didn't care if
they ever came back!
This is my fault!
Drown, monster, drown!
Hey, who died?
My parents, probably.
So you guys aren't
ice cream men?
If my parents are lost at sea,
are you gonna find 'em?
We'll try, but have you ever
been to the sea?
It's huge.
And we have to search all of them--
'cause they all,you know, connect.
Don't worry, boy.
They'll find your parents soon.
And until they do, you can stay here.
And we'll move your bedtime
to an hour later,
so you'll have more time to
be alone with your thoughts.
Hey, hey, come on.
Why don't you cheer up
with a glass of Ocean Spray?
Oh, boy forget that.
How about some...?
Cap'n crunch
Uh, Seven Seas Italian dressing?
Ooh! No, no!
Uh, Chicken of the Sea tuna?
Billy Ocean CD?
The History of Atlantic Records?
Stop naming things!
I want to, but I can't!
Then go to Moe's!
Good idea.
I'll drown my sorrows
in Anchor Steam Beer.
Oh! I'm sorry...
Why don't we do something special for you
get you all snazzed up.
Like I'm going to a funeral?
No! Don't talk like that!
There's always hope.
We just wanted to let you know,
we've stopped searching.
This'll cheer you up.
I'll let you kill me in Bar Brawl Four: Final Fracas.
Take that I'll cut ya...!
Uh-oh. I slipped on some blood.
I'm totally vulnerable to
a full-body jukebox slam.
Oh, come on, it's easy.
Just push A, B, up, up, left trigger,
right trigger, and both triggers at once.
Isn't there already enough pain in this world?
Let's just pay the check and go.
Thanks, Mags.
I could use a pick-me-up.
Oh, my God.
I've become the world's oldest baby.
Men don't get their moo-moo from a ba-ba.
They get their moo-moo
from a big-boy cup!
I can't be a baby anymore.
I'm alone now.
I have to be a man!
Thanks, Mags.
Where is it?
I gotta find out what
color Marge's eyes are.
Ah...
Cha-ching!
Oh!
Oh, Marge, darling,
what's the combination
to our wedding album?
Our anniversary!
D'oh!
All right, Dragon's Eye,
may your path be true
and your caroms many.
Just shoot!
Uh-oh, it's rolling to wards that loner!
Who is it?
It's Milhouse!
That's not the Milhouse I know.
Ha! ha!
You know Milhouse!
Okay, everyone.
My best friend
is a little messed up,
so everyone
be extra nice to him.
Hey, loser, your mom called.
One day, you'll be more haunted
by those words than I am.
Why aren't you crying?
I wish I could cry.
Tears would cleanse my soul.
Oh, Milhouse!
You're very brave.
Go ahead, beat me up.
Maybe then I'll feel something.
Eh, what's the point?
Milhouse, that was the bravest
thing I've ever seen.
I always wanted you
to hold my hand, Lisa.
And now that you are, I'm
too numb to feel anything.
It's like you're wearing oven mitts
and I'm in my winter parka.
That's so poetic.
Looks like you're not the coolest
kid in school anymore.
Hey, I'm happy to see Milhouse
get some hand-on-hand action.
But no one is cooler than
Bartholomew J. Simpson.
Really?
See ya at lunch.
Anyone want to sit over here?
You can have my pizza crust.
Young man, you look like
you enjoy fun and excitement.
Please, Bart, you're
embarrassing yourself.
Milhouse, call me
if you need to talk.
If you want to come to my place,
I've got a squirrel in a shoebox.
I'm just sayin'...
Thanks, but I want to take
a walk alone...
...and work some stuff out.
Come on!
Look at me, I'm cool.
I've got my backpack on frontwards,
and I'm krumping!
Check it out!
This image has not been speed up.
There's a time for krumping,
and this isn't it.
I'll krump with you, sweetie pie.
Look at these poll numbers.
Ay, caramba!
Oh, man.
Milhouse has gone from being
a comic figure to a tragic one.
If he could go back to being happy,
I could go back to being cool.
Boy, stop talking to yourself.
Your thoughts should stay
in your head.
I sure told him.
Now what am I going
to do about Marge?
Let's see.
Milhouse would be happy again
if he had family to take care of him.
Family, family.
Every Christmas...
Milhouse gets
Danish butter cookies from...
Solvang, California...
where he has a beloved un... cle!
Directory assistance for Solvang,
a little bit of Denmark
on California's central coast.
We have three Van Houtens.
Fine, I'll call three numbers.
What are they?
Butter cookie 8-2147,
Hans Christian Anderson 5-5166,
and Aquavit 3-2599.
Okay, so which one of these losers
is Milhouse's Uncle Norbert?
Norbert? Norbert?
Oh, this guy's a total Norbert.
Norbert? I wish.
My name is Gaylord Q. Tinkledink.
Bart, I'm Norbert Van Houten,
but everyone calls me Zack.
You're Uncle Norbert?
Well, I'm one
of the Danish Van Houtens,
not the Dutch Van Houtens.
Now, my nephew Milhouse needs
me and I'm here for him.
And I'm here to find my nephew
Nerdletaub Z. Pantybottom.
Let us join forces.
Would you be my uncle?
No, but have a butter cookie.
Milhouse, there's someone
who wants to see you.
Uncle Zack?
Milhouse, your parents may be
gone, but I'm here for you now.
Well, I don't need you.
I've learned to take care of myself.
I see.
You've become quite a young man--
self-reliant, mature.
You've shed your Dutch ways
and become a true Dane.
But, uh, perhaps you're not too cool
to give your uncle a hug?
I promise you won't be
alone anymore, son.
And that takes care of that.
Oh, man, now he's
even more popular.
He's troubled, but I can save him.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Oh, I'll never remember
what color Marge's eyes are.
Uh... brown? No.
Orange? No.
Elm? Rake?
Guessing?
Well, well, look who's strolling
down Alzheimer Avenue.
You used to know everything
about that wife of yours,
even wrote a song about her.
A song?
Wait, it's coming back to me.
The girl I love's
got beautiful hair
A blue bouffant
From here to there
Snow white teeth and lips so red
She's the Wilma to my Fred
Oh, the girl I love's got beautiful...
Eyes
When happy, they sparkle,
when sad, they cries
Those eyes are gems beyond appraisal
Stunning shade of purest...
Oh, what is it?
I was so close.
Let's see, what rhymes
with appraisal?
Basil, nasal.
None of these are colors.
Oh, it's hopeless.
She'll never love me again.
Oh, Homie.
I'd forgotten that beautiful
song you wrote for me.
Hazel!
Your eyes are hazel.
Hazel like the pussy willows
by the pond where we first kissed,
like the almond paste
in the bear claw I ate
after we first made love.
Milhouse, that was a perfect landing.
Oh, did you remember to
cut off the gas flow?
The what?
Lis, I don't get it.
Why does Milhouse's happiness
make me sad?
Bart, Bart, Bart.
You're worried
you're losing Milhouse,
and love is a selfish thing.
Shut up! I don't love Milhouse.
Oh, really?
The more you deny it,
the more I know it's true.
Oh, yeah? Well, when you're mean,
I'm a trampoline,
so everything you said goes
back and hits your ugly head.
God, that was lame.
Where did you get that?
From Milhouse!
Oh, I love him so much!
Aw, it's okay.
Students, I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
The coolest student in school,
Milhouse Van Houten,
is leaving us.
He and his uncle,
who is also very cool,
will be returning to Solvang
forever via hot air balloon.
Our trip will be fraught
with hardship and peril,
but it still beats third-period
gym with Mr. Johnson.
Hey, in the real world,
rope-climbing skills are vital.
Good-bye, old life.
Wait, Milhouse!
Don't go!
You're my best friend.
I have to go.
Well, then I'm going with you.
Bart, climb up.
I... can't.
Well, what do you think of
Mr. Johnson's rope-climbing class now?
- Still sucks!
- Come on.
So who's up for a
trip around the world?
I am, I am!
If we can catch the trade winds,
we'll be in the Florida Keys
by tomorrow morning.
I can't wait to see our little...
Milhouse!
Mom and Dad!
Mr. and Mrs. Van Houten!
Damned Dutchmen!
I'm so glad you're alive!
I'll never have to be
self-reliant again.
Not so fast, son.
We are trapped on this island.
No worries. I've already
radioed for a rescue boat
sailed by brave Danish sailors.
More like swishy Danish sailors.
You're going down, Dutchman.
You grapple like a girl!
Transcript : Raceman
Traduction : Skualler, Rassman
Synchro : Job22, Daffy
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net