The D'oh Team présente...
Traduction : Kenji,
Synchro : Kenji, sw38
Relecture : Bartelemix, Sebaset
Thanks to swsub.com
for the transcript.
All right,
next on my shopping list...
a new phone.
Attention, shoppers,
Iphone is now 20 cents.
What happened to that
mini-cell phone I gave you, Sir ?
Ooh, I thought it
was a lemon drop.
I'll go get
the number de-listed.
Well, well.
What have we here ?
Why do I need another penny ?
I have Billions.
Still, if I don't take it,
that hoodlum over there might.
All right, penny,
prepare to be pinched.
Come to Papa.
Help...me !
Help me !
I guess this is the end.
I just wish, i had spent more time
at the office.
Hey, you're not a penny !
You saved my life !
There must be something,
I can do for you ?
A cookie ! No, a car !
No, a cookie !
You're getting a free dinner.
- With...  - Yeah ?
- Me !
"Me" ? But that's you !
I'll pick you up
at 5:00 tomorrow.
And I'll pick you up
right now.
Got It.
See you at 5:00, then.
Dinner with Mr. Burns...
what a waste of my precious,
precious, Saturday night.
Hey dad ! Have fun
with your boyfriend.
He is not my boyfriend !
So, Simpson,
I hear you like pizza pie.
I do.
- My favorite is chicago deep-dish.
- Chicago, eh ?
Well... What if I took us
there now ?
Drive to Chicago ?
I don't have time for that.
I have to be back at work on Monday,
and my boss is a total jerk.
Who said anything about drive ?
A p-private jet !
Now would you care for some sushi ?
Uh, yeah, but i'm on a plane, idiot.
My name is Svetlana,
but you can call me, "Hey Baby."
And just so you know,...
she'll do anything for you.
Anything except sex !
And i do mean, anything.
Ooh, I'm aroused...
and confused.
... Scratchy Show !
Stewardess !
Sorry, everyone.
Air traffic control says we have
to spend another three hours...
on the tarmac.
This is wonderful.
Now, why don't you listen
to the musical stylings...
of Mr. Lionel Richie ?
Oh, my God ! Lionel Richie !
Can you sing "Say You Say Me",
but make it about beer ?
Sure, I guess.
Hey, you, beer me.
Beer me for always.
That's the way it should be.
Hey, you, beer me.
Beer us together...
naturally.
Now make every word beer !
Beer, beer.
Beer, Beer
Beer, beer, beer, beer.
Huh, wait i forgot the word.
Love you.
If i leave the plane,
i'll be just like every one else !
Ground control,
this is November 543 Charlie.
We're gonna need the extractor.
I want to be back on the plane.
We'll be back before you know it.
Svetlana ! Svetlana !
Now let's enjoy
the Miami of Canada...
Chicago !
Okay, folks !
For our first improv...
we gonna need an occupation.
Billionaire !
Oh, oh, Nice job !
Where do I apply ?
Now, i need a location.
I came to relax.
You think of it.
I hear " a Starbucks...in Siberia".
Killer premise.
Finally, an emotion.
Drunk !
Okay, "drunk".
And now we take you
to a drunken billionaire...
at a Starbucks in Siberia.
Uh, excuse me.
I need a, I need a coffee.
Can you change
a billion dollar bill ?
Our coffee costs a billion dollars.
This is Starbucks.
In Siberia.
Why are you applauding them ?
We wrote it.
While you were here,
we felt like New York !
I'm so happy.
Homer, you smell like Chicago.
Did fly there
on a commercial airline ?
No way ! Commercial is for losers
and terrorists.
I flew on a private plane.
It is much different
from a normal plane ?
Please, tell me you're joking.
It's the difference between
champagne and carbonated pee.
Homie, what's wrong ?
I had it all for one night.
Now for the rest of my life,
i'll know what i'm missing.
And all i have to remember it by...
is that my ears haven't popped.
Well, i'll make sure that
I never yawn again !
Hey, Homer.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi.
High like a private plane ?
The kind I'll never be
invited to ride on again.
That's where
you're wrong, Homer.
A fresh face!
This is Colby Krause.
I hired him to help you,
improve your life.
He'll get you back on
a private plane in no time.
No way.
I don't need any shrink,
therapist,...
counselor, motivational
speaker or "guru. "
I'm a life coach.
Oh, tell me more.
The first step in self-improvement...
is to take a thorough
look at your life.
If you're gonna film me,...
I insist on a body double.
Is uncle fester still alive ?
- The camera is not done yet right ?
- No.
Okay, now I just want you to do...
what you normally do.
Okay.
Well, uh...
Hmm, I'll just, hu...
I forget what i do.
Wait, what ?
Uh, this is some
of what I do... I think.
Sometimes I go places.
This is our relish tray.
I'd like you to film it
for insurance purposes.
Oh, what's the point
of putting my socks on ?
I just have to take them off
again a week later.
Homer, before you even
head out the door, in the morning,...
you're already a loser.
Fine, I'll show you a winner,
just you watch.
Think positive, think positive.
You were saying ?
Homer, your journey downstairs
would've been a lot safer...
if you'd rembered
the NDCs of concentration:
Never Don't Concentrate.
Will you shut up ?
I can't hear the song
in my head!
Do you want to get a
reaction shot of his butt?
No, but we should
get some background noise.
Everyone quiet for four seconds.
Thank you people.
Moving on.
What ?
Here's an important tip:
Stop doing that.
I really enjoyed
paying you to yell at me...
and say I suck,
but it's no use.
I'm a hopeless loser
and always will be.
Homer, you're up!
This I can do!
- Whoa ! Boom !
- Way to go !
Behold my 217
average and weep.
As I said,
I've lost all hope.
Homer, here in
the bowling alley,...
you're a totally
different man...
relaxed, confident...
Is this going somewhere?
But what we have to do
is figure a way...
to make "Bowling Alley Homer"
into "Everyday Homer. "
I have an aunt
who became an uncle.
Is it like that?
I want you to wear
those bowling shoes...
out the door and
everywhere you go.
It's crazy, but
it just might work.
Dr. Fredrick J. Waxman,
you're a genius!
That's not my name.
I wasn't talking to you.
Homer, your shoe attitude...
is bowling people over.
These are letters
from companies...
interested in
interviewing you !
How many of those
have private planes ?
This one !
"Handyman's Choice
Copper Tubing" ?
They need
a safety inspector to fly...
between their North American plants.
I'm getting that job.
Bart, I'll need some clean urine.
Stat.
Now to make sure you're
motivated to get this job,...
you have to quit
your old one.
I'll call your boss right now.
I'll get it, sir.
Just send it
to voice mail.
You here for the
safety inspector job ?
Well, i can see
the position of handsomest CEO...
is already taken.
I like you already.
If you can write your name
so I can read it, you're in.
I got the job !
Yay, Dad !
We knew you could do it !
Good luck
on your first day, Dad.
Give 'em
hell, Homer.
We're all so proud
of you, sweetie.
I'm gonna get there early,
so I can get in good...
with the lunch truck guy.
Find out if he
has a wife !
We could double date !
- Yay, Dad !
- You're a Hero.
Can I help you ?
Uh, yeah. I have no
job and nowhere to go.
What do I have to buy
so I can sit here all day ?
Well, with a coffee,
you can stay till lunch.
Then you have
to order a solid.
One small
coffee, please.
And a dozen of those
placemats with the maze on it.
They're all the same maze.
Somebody's got to do 'em.
Look happy.
So, how was your first day
at your new job ?
Oh, it was great !
Flew to Tulsa
on the company jet.
Did my job in a way consistent
with what I already told you.
Because, that's what you do.
When you have a job !
I'm so proud of you, Dad !
Stop peppering me
with questions !
Principal Skinner !
Why did we have to leave...
the Learn and Touch
Reptile Zoo so early ?
Well, it seems
someone was riding...
the giant tortoise naked.
It's not my fault.
The drinking fountain
dared me to do it.
Freak fry !
Look out
If it touches you,
you die of suicide !
Don't do it ! Don't do it !
Dad ?
I know it's you, Homer.
Why aren't you
at your new job ?
Well, explanation-wise,
the fact is that...
I lied.
I didn't get the job.
You see when
I got there.
So, she said,
"That's not my in-box,"...
and he said,
"That's not the Johnson Report !"
You sure know how to repeat
the joke I just told ya.
But as a formality, I must ask :
Do you know
anything about copper tubing ?
Come on, say
"You're hired"!
Say it !
Leave your resume with Cheryl.
Security ! Security !
Stop saying
"Security"!
Come on,
just give me the job.
I like your hat.
Just say the word !
I couldn't bear to
tell your mother,...
so I hang out
here all day.
But, Dad,
you gotta tell her.
She's been buying
brand-name groceries.
Brands like "Miser's Choice"
and "Day-Old Delights"?
No, things
rich people buy,...
like Campbell's Soup
and Pepsodent.
Hello ?
Honey, there's something
I have to tell you.
It's bad news, isn't it ?
I should never get my hopes up.
Nothing ever works out for us.
No, it's, uh...
- good news !
- Really ?
We're manufacturing
a new pipe diameter,...
five-eights inch.
The company wants you and me
to take the private plane...
to New York for the premiere !
So meet me at Shelbyville
Airport in an hour.
If I'm gonna tell
that woman the truth,...
I'm going to do it
in the one place...
no one can ever be sad.
Okay. So this should be
enough money...
to get me up in the air,
have a frank talk with Marge,...
then maybe eat a deviled egg.
Well, anything,
for a fellow Marine.
Yeah, semper fudge
Uh, did you just say
"Semper fudge"?
No, I said the
right thing.
Look at this business center...
fax, Wi-Fi, teleconferencing
capabilities.
I'm gonna remember
this day for the rest of my life !
Uh, honey...
don't try to remember the whole day.
Just what you're
feeling this second.
Sweetheart, what do you mean?
Marge, I gotta be honest...
- What was that ?
- I don't know.
Maybe, we flew through a rainbow.
I didn't think I'd be flying today,
so I was doing heroin.
Homie, what are you doing ?
You don't know how to fly !
I drove a car over a cliff once.
How different could it be ?
Hmm, what's the ocean doing
in the sky ?
There's only one man
who can help us now.
Hello, and welcome to success.
It's Marge Simpson.
I need you to coach like
you've never coached before !
Marge, please,
I'm with a client.
Now you listen
here, bub !
We paid you all the savings
we had in the world.
You could at least tell my
husband something encouraging.
All right, Homer.
What is it you're attempting to do ?
Win over a difficult client ?
I'm trying to land a plane
with no experience.
Homer, I gotta tell you
I'm not very good.
I went to the Harvard
of the South.
Duke? That's good.
- Not Duke.
- Vanderbilt ?
A little further South.
Don't make me say it.
Duffman has reported you
to the FAA.
This near miss will be
investigated...
by a board of three
retired pilots.
Okay, Homer,
i don't know anything about planes,...
but I know about you.
You have what made America great :
No understanding of the limits
of your power,...
and a complete lack of concern
for what anyone thinks of you.
So you'll land that plane.
And do you know why ?
Because I heard some guy say
you couldn't.
What ? I'll show him.
I'll show that guy !
Elevation 300 feet, 200 feet,
50 feet...
Homer, you did it !
You landed a jet !
Now, to taxi to the terminal.
Marge, flying in private jets
is great and all,...
but it's just too dangerous.
That's why I've decided
to go to the plant...
and beg Mr. Burns
for my old job back.
I understand, Homie.
And at least we can take...
the extra income you've earned
in the last few months...
and set it aside for a rainy day.
You'd think so, but no.
Mr. Richie, your American Music
Awards are weighing us down !
Let them go !
You let yours go !
I don't have any.
That's right, you don't !
www.tvsubtitles.net