Sync by NightWalker
(laughs)
You've fallen right
into my trap,
just like you
did in Africa.
Krusty, there you are.
We've got business
to discuss.
First off,
we got big problems
with your talking
home pregnancy tests.
Hey-hey, you're pregnant
and it's not mine!
(laughing)
It's giving 20%
false "hey-heys."
Oh, okay, uh,
repackage them
as coffee stirrers and sell
them in the Philippines.
Genius.
Now, another issue:
Studies show
your Krusty Burger
is the unhealthiest fast-food
item in the world.
Worse than
the Double Krusty Burger?
Somehow, yes.
Okay, here's what we do.
What's that food we never
put in any of our meals?
Vegetables?
Yeah, those guys.
Find the cheapest one,
and make a burger
out of it.
Then throw it in a green
wrapper and double the price.
And say it's got
none of those, uh,
what are those unhealthy
he-she sounding things?
Uh, trans fats?
That's it!
And while you're in there,
spray a little nicotine juice
on the kids' meals.
Get 'em hooked.
(laughs)
ANNOUNCER:
Coming up on:
(crewman shouting)
(grunting)
It was worth it
to be on TV!
Put our dying screams
in the promo!
(both screaming)
You know, kids,
the real drowningest
catch is man.
It's a new world out there.
People care about their health,
for some reason.
We know times have changed.
And we at Krusty Burger want
to take advantage of that.
Introducing...
the Mother Nature Burger.
Made from 100%
wheat-fed barley.
And now to take a yummy bite.
Mmm... tastes like
a healthy future.
We're going
to Krusty Burger!
Finally, a hamburger
for the Hindus.
By the tusks of great Ganesh,
now no one can tell
I am not American.
(sitar music plays, Apu chants)
Look at me!
I'm saving the Earth!
Where's my Nobel prize?
(bubbly rumbling)
What's wrong, old friend?
Can't sleep?
(rumbling continues)
Aww.
Would some warm beer
settle you down?
(rumbling continues)
Uh-oh.
Those barley burgers
were tainted!
Why did I eat 12 of them? Why?!
Taken!
Occupied!
Hurling!
(muffled):
Uh-oh.
(teachers and kids groaning)
SKINNER (over P.A.):
Attention, students,
due to the recent
queasiness,
both the Presidential
Ab-Crunch Challenge
and the Sloppy Joe-A-Thon
have been cancelled.
(weakly):
Skinner!
If I die,
I want you to take over...
Really?
...the search committee
for a new superintendent.
Mm...
Just hold my head and
say soothing things.
Third-grade math scores
are holding steady.
Ah, yes...
The food poisoning
has been traced
to a single ingredient:
tainted barley.
And where does that
barley come from?
Our neighbor to the southeast,
Ogdenville.
The state's barley basket
since it was settled
100 years ago,
by Norwegian immigrants.
I'm here with barley farmer
Brendlf Jensen. Brendlf?
What happened is,
a big ol' rat got caught up
in the grinders there, so my
wife, Dagny, took a hose to it.
And, uh, it's all
cleaned out now.
So you're
guaranteeing it's safe
to eat Ogdenville barley
once more?
Well, where there's barley,
there's rats, you know.
Now, when will you
be starting the interview?
That just went out live.
Well, then we're screwed.
(slow, melancholy
orchestral theme playing)
Dad, are you
sure you can
put in these new rain
gutters all by yourself?
Eh, maybe you're right.
I do have a bad history
of going up on roofs
and waking up in hospitals.
Perhaps we could be
of help, don't you know.
Ogdenvillians?
Work on my house?
Ja. Ever since
the barley bust,
the only work we can get
is day labor.
We don't mind it.
Work is work.
I like your
can-do attitude!
And your facial hair screams
rugged but reliable.
You won't regret
this, sir.
You hear that, Bart?
He called me "sir."
That means he knows
I'm better than him.
Nicely done, guys.
Lemonade?
A lemon version
of barley-ade?
(chuckles):
When in Springfield...
Oh, don't that glug
down right good then.
Oh, ja, almost
as good as barley-ade.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, ja. Oh, ja.
You know, I'm glad
you've come here
to take all the jobs
we don't want to do.
Can't have too much
of a good thing.
OGDENVILLIAN:
You fellas, too, come on!
( music playing throughout )
( women vocalizing )
So, Inga, this
is our kitchen.
Did you have kitchens
back in Ogdenville?
Ja, before the dark days
fell on my people
and we lost everything.
Great! So you know your
way around a blender.
Okay, so if the dog's
in the house,
don't let Grampa
in and vice versa.
Our neighbor, Ned Flanders,
drops by unexpectedly.
That I do!
But he doesn't stay long.
No, I don't!
Kids, this is Inga,
your new nanny.
A nanny? Whoo-hoo!
Mom says I can have ice cream
for breakfast.
Oh, she's still here.
Mom, can I have
ice cream for breakfast?
No way, mister.
It's just chocolate chip
pancakes and syrup for you.
Inga, I'll be happy
to eat whatever you make.
(frustrated grunt)
Maggie, now you have a nanny.
Just like the ones
Joe Piscopo
and Ethan Hawke
left their wives for.
But hands off my Homie.
Hands off the Homie.
Got it.
(whimpers)
Sorry, sometimes
she's nervous
around new people.
Actually,
she's just gassy.
A little lingonberry oil
under the tongue will clear it
right up.
(Maggie coos, burbles)
That's amazing!
Now I feel bad about
calling your references.
So Selma,
how did you meet?
I hired Torbjorn, here,
to kill some moles
in my garden.
And, well, one thing
led to another...
Ja, she has the same
beautiful face
as my great-uncle Magnus
when he lay in the coffin
after his trolley
accident.
Gee, this
Ogdenville influx
has been great
for everybody.
Yeah, talk about taking jobs
Springfield don't want!
(laughs)
Hey, Homer, your blubber
would light our
lamps for a year.
D'oh!
I zing the oaf good?
You zing the oaf great.
Minnesota Vikings apparel?!
This is Tennessee
Titans country!
Waah!
Uff da!
So many meters.
(kids agreeing)
Step aside, Nor-wads.
Watch how the natives ride sky.
(The Chantays'
"Pipeline" begins)
(yells)
(groans)
Three hours and we still
can't see a doctor?!
It's 'cause it's filled
with all these Nor-wads.
They even sneeze funny.
(sneezing):
A-fer-gan-nerkin!
We're out of English forms.
You'll have to fill out
a Norwegian one.
I can't read this
sloopy-bloopy writing.
Typical-- foreigners
clogging up the system.
I hurt my back unclogging
your septic system.
Sven, can you stop
by tomorrow?
It's clogged again.
Ja.
Come on, Bart.
We'll take care
of you at home.
(sneezing):
Na-chin-na-hart!
Oh great, I
caught their cold.
Okay, Bart.
Now bite down on the
rubber dog bone, and...
(toy squeaks,
bone snaps)
Mm!
(barks)
Thanks, Mom.
Now, how did this
happen again?
It wasn't my fault.
I swear.
A couple of barleyjerks
dared me to.
Yeah, well, I'm starting
to wonder if this town
wasn't better off before all
these immigrants showed up.
I'd just like to remind you
that we were all immigrants
at one time.
Well, you were a baby once.
Does that mean you still
like milk and hugs?
Yes, I'd like both right now.
(grunts)
Hey, this is all right.
(humming tune)
Look at them barleyjacks,
celebrating another one
of their stupid holidays.
Hey, I ain't got no
problem with them.
They pay in cash,
they keep it clean,
and their mythology is
rich and enchanting.
Yeah, and the redhead one
said today's the day
Woden gave the herring
the greatest gift of all--
its fishy taste.
Hey, Moe, what is that
hoity-toity beer
they're drinking?
Oh, I don't sell
beer no more.
I only serve Aquavit,
the Norwegian caraway-scented
liqueur.
Wait a minute-- you're
selling barleyjack booze?
How could you, Moe?!
Hey, it's all about
the King Haralds.
Well, since it's all you've got,
give me a mug of that
Aquavit stuff.
Better go slow
there, friend.
That stuff will open up a can
of "oh my goodness" on you.
I think I can handle it.
(drunkenly):
Hey, where'd that Homer guy go?
(muffled):
More Aquavit, please.
(groans)
(drunkenly):
Farfegnugen...
You're late.
And drunk.
Shut up.
You lost your job?
It's not my fault.
Those Ogdenville guys plied me
with their native liqueurs
and liquors.
But mostly liqueurs.
Oh, poor Homie.
And you with
your alcoholism.
Yeah.
I propose that no
Ogdenvillian be allowed
within the city limits
of Springfield.
I share your xylophobia.
Dad, you mean
xenophobia.
Xylophobia would be
a fear of xylophones.
I am afraid of xylophones.
It's the music you hear
when skeletons are dancing.
Very well.
Springfield will ban
immigrants and xylophones.
All in favor, say "Aye."
ALL:
Aye!
The border is now closed.
You'll never take my xylophone.
Notes don't fail me now.
(playing rapidly)
There's one, Chief.
Well, he's too far, Lou.
That's not fair.
There's another.
He's on a bike, Lou.
So?
So what am I, Superman?
Well, there's one coming
between your legs.
Where?
There! Now!
Right now, look
between your legs!
I don't-- Oh, oh yeah.
Oh, ow, ow...
No, he's too fast.
It's hopeless, Lou.
We can't handle this.
We need help
patrolling the border.
I mean, Springfield
only has three cops.
Yeah. And Eddie's laid up
'cause of his gout.
(groans)
Yep. Eddie loves his
lobster and port wine,
but it comes with a price.
Excuse me: do you have to pay
to get in, or...?
No, no, no, it's
free, it's free.
Maybe we can ask private
citizens to guard the border.
Yeah, you know, vigilantes
who would agree to do our job
for the adrenaline rush
that comes from having
a tiny taste of authority
over your fellow man.
And all we're paying 'em
is bullets and beer.
(chuckles)
I almost made a big mistake.
Men, our negative energy
has been harnessed
to help keep Springfield's
borders secure
from Ogdenvillians.
But first, our group
needs a name
that evokes America's proud
history of citizens rising up
to defend our way of life.
The Klan?
Well, there are no bad ideas,
but let's keep trying.
The Nazis?
Okay, you stop trying.
Hey, how about the Star-Spangled
Goofballs?
Mm! Goofballs it is!
I'll float above the border,
and radio the location
of illegals down to you.
My code name will be
"Screaming Eagle."
Yours will be "Ground Losers."
What a fun day.
This is gonna
be good.
Release the sandbags.
Hey, why don't you
let Carl and me try?
Okay, you guys get
in as I get off.
(yelling)
This is Ground Loser.
What's your position?
Over.
C-c-cold.
S-s-so very cold.
I'm sorry to say that this
poorly-conceived patrol
carried out by a group
of rank amateurs
has somehow been a failure.
Those barleyjacks are crafty.
One of 'em handcuffed me
to this tree.
That's not a
tree, Chief.
That's a street sign.
You just looped
your belt around it
when you were
changing your pants.
Okay, I'm hearing lots of
problems, but no solutions.
This immigration problem is
bigger than we thought.
We need a way to keep these
people out of our community.
What can we do to keep
one group of people
away from another
group of people?
HOMER:
Why you little...!
I'll kill you!
That's it--
we'll build a fence.
CROWD (chanting):
Fence! Fence! Fence! Fence!
Homie, I don't think we
should build a fence.
Haven't we always taught
the children to make friends
with those who are
a little different?
Yes.
Yeah.
Ja!
(gasps)
Ja, ja!
Maggie's first words
are in Ogdenvillese!
Now do you see, Marge?
Now do you see why we
must build that fence?
Build it, Homie!
Make it as tall as the sky
and deeper than Hell.
Ja. Ja.
All right, who here knows
how to build a wall?
I know how to hire guys
to build a wall.
Such as?
The Barleyjacks?
(all agreeing)
Okay, they can help,
us build the wall,
because they're good at it.
But then, those
good-for-nothings have to go.
(cheering)
Yeah, get 'em
out of here!
(Benny Goodman's
"Sing, Sing, Sing" playing)
So my girlfriend puts all
these pillows on the bed.
And you have to like take
them all off at night
and put them all back
on every morning.
And if the little one is
in back of the big one,
oh, God help you.
Ja, and they always want the
cat to sleep in bed with you.
Exactly.
I had trouble finding a
four-button cardigan,
so I bought
a three-button one
and sewed the extra
button on myself.
Hm! This baby was
a five-buttoner,
but I took a button off.
Maybe we're not so
different, Sven.
Ja, maybe so.
You know, if you put
down an acrylic primer,
your satiric drawing
and its clever stink
lines will be there
long after your
principal is gone.
The guy at the store
said it didn't matter,
but I knew he was wrong.
Thanks, man.
(all shouting)
(clang echoing)
(wind whistling)
(Ralph giggling)
Sure is quiet around here.
Do ya miss us?
Ja, we miss you.
That's why we build
the door.
Oh, we did miss you.
We missed your kindness,
your hard work,
your sweet plainspoken ways.
What are you barleyjacks
waiting for?
Get in here!
We'd be more than pleased
to join you donut-dunkers.
(lively chatter
and laughter)
(siren wailing)
All right, boys,
round 'em up...
and throw them the swingingest
soiree they've ever seen!
(lively Scandanavian
folk music playing)
www.tvsubtitles.net